krishijagran.com 2017-12-19

# Privacy Policy

For us privacy for our valued customer is very important. We strongly believe that the personal information of our customers should not be shared with the third party without the prior consent or request from the customer. Privacy is the right of an individual and at MAC KRISHI JAGRAN the information of the customer such as contact no., email, addresses etc is used only for the internal purpose and not for sale. Your contact information is stored in our database and is only used to contact you during the course of your stay with us for sharing the status of your room bookings with us and then after for announcement of our latest deals and news etc. We at MAC KRISHI JAGRAN condemn the unauthorized reach and misuse and/or discloser of the personal information of the customer and we have strict guidelines and high security features to prevent the same. Any changes in our ‘Privacy Policy’ will be posted here on the website. **SECURE ONLINE PAYMENTS**

The visitor on our website please take a note that your name, email address and other personal information submitted on our website may be stored with us and may also appear on the website. Like other platforms our server log files also receives general information such as IP address of the visitor, cookie etc. For the financial transactions by credit card MAC KRISHI JAGRAN uses a 3rd party secure payment gateway provided by “PayU” and the credit card details are ‘not stored’ with MAC KRISHI JAGRAN, instead the information is securely stored and encrypted with Visa/MasterCard. **Smart Cookies**

We use 'Cookies' to keep track of your current shopping session to personalize your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping cart at any time. 'Cookies' are tiny text files which our Website places on your computer's hard drive to store information about your shopping session and to identify your computer.
